<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cPanel ELevate CentOS 7 to AlmaLinux 8 on cPanel elevate documentation</title>
    <link>https://cpanel.github.io/elevate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cPanel ELevate CentOS 7 to AlmaLinux 8 on cPanel elevate documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 08:53:47 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cpanel.github.io/elevate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Known cPanel ELevate Blockers</title>
      <link>https://cpanel.github.io/elevate/blockers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 16:13:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cpanel.github.io/elevate/blockers/</guid>
      <description>Known Blockers The following is a list of install states which the script will intentionally prevent you from upgrading with. This is because the script cannot garantuee a successful upgrade with these conditions in place.
Basic checks The following conditions are assumed to be in place any time you run this script:
 You have CentOS 7.9 or greater installed.  We DO NOT support alternative RHEL 7 (including CloudLinux) variants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Paper</title>
      <link>https://cpanel.github.io/elevate/whitepaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 08:53:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cpanel.github.io/elevate/whitepaper/</guid>
      <description>download a pdf version of this white paper
Abstract cPanel, L.L.C. has embraced the ELevate project [1], an open-source initiative by the AlmaLinux OS Foundation (“AlmaLinux”) to help users perform upgrades between different Red Hat® Enterprise Linux® (RHEL)-derivative distributions. This white paper captures the relevant details in evaluating the ELevate process to upgrade a cPanel &amp;amp; WHM® server from a RHEL-derived distribution version 7.x to an AlmaLinux distribution version 8.x. The intended audience for this paper are the decision-makers who may be considering upgrading their cPanel &amp;amp; WHM servers to a different RHEL-based distribution.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
